- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob
SquarePants!
海绵宝宝
方裤！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
海绵宝宝！
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[cheering, chatter]
[欢呼声、议论声]
- Perch Perkins here
- 鲈鱼帕金斯在这里
for Bikini Bottom News.
比基尼泳裤新闻。
Today SpongeBob SquarePants
will attempt the impossible:
今天海绵宝宝
会尝试不可能的事情：
a high-sea dive
from that diving board!
公海潜水
从那个跳水板上！
He'll be the first sponge ever
to dive up through the ocean.
他将成为史上第一块海绵
潜入海洋。
- Mow.
- 哞。
- Did you hear
what Perch said, Gary?
- 你听到了吗
珀奇说什么，加里？
The first sponge!
第一个海绵！
- Whoa.
- 哇哦。
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
- Pretty cool, huh, kid?
- 很酷吧，孩子？
- Ahh!
- 啊！
Okay, Gary, that's enough lard.
好吧，加里，猪油就够了。
I gotta warm up.
我得热身一下。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[straining]
[紧张]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Whaa--oh!
哇——哦！
That's good.
I'm all warmed up.
那挺好的。
我都热身了。
- Get your SpongeBob
standees here!
- 获取你的海绵宝宝
站在这里！
Buy one and take home a hero!
买一个，带一个英雄回家！
Here you are, here!
Here!
你在这里，在这里！
这里！
- [sobbing]
- [抽泣]
- Hey, SpongeBob.
What's new?
- 嘿，海绵宝宝。
什么是新的？
Oh, so that's how it is, huh?
哦，原来是这样啊？
The silent treatment.
沉默的对待。
Well, two can play
at that game, mister!
还好两个人可以玩
在那场比赛中，先生！
[huffs]
- Excuse me.
[怒气]
- 对不起。
How much for this stupid
star fish standee?
这个傻子多少钱
星鱼站着吗？
- Hmm?
- 唔？
Hmm.
[giggles]
唔。
[咯咯笑]
20 bucks?
20块钱？
- [grunts]
But it's damaged.
- [咕哝]
但它已损坏。
- 10 bucks?
- 10 块钱？
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
- Sold!
- 卖！
[munching, gulp]
[咀嚼，吞咽]
- [belches]
- [打嗝]
[crowd shouting]
[人群喊叫]
- Hi--uh!
- 嗨——呃！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- And here's our hero now
- 现在这是我们的英雄
with the flag
he will plant on the surface.
与旗帜
他将在表面上种植。
- Thank you! Thank you!
- 谢谢你！谢谢你！
Thank you!
谢谢你！
[drumroll]
[鼓声]
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
Ahh!
啊！
Ooh.
哦。
[crowd groans, murmurs]
[人群呻吟，低语]
- Get your SpongeBob standees
right here.
- 获取你的海绵宝宝立像
就在这里。
Buy one and take home
a loser.
买一个带回家
一个失败者。
- I just don't understand it.
- 我只是不明白。
Surface divers go down.
水面潜水员下潜。
Why didn't I go up?
我怎么没上去？
- Well, back in Texas,
Olympic divers
- 好吧，回到德克萨斯州，
奥运跳水运动员
have gravity
to help them go down.
有重力
帮助他们下去。
What you need
is anti-gravity to go up.
你需要什么
是反重力上去的。
- Anti-gravity? Yes!
- 反重力？是的！
Yah!
啊！
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
- Hmph. Stupid messy moron
rubbernecking flounders
- 哼。愚蠢又凌乱的白痴
橡皮颈比目鱼
and so on...
等等...
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
- I'm doing it! I'm doing it!
- 我正在做！我正在做！
♪ ♪
Ahh...
啊...
♪ ♪
I'm the first
high-sea-diving sponge.
我是第一个
远海潜水海绵。
[groans]
[呻吟]
♪ ♪
Hey, what happened
to the surface?
嘿，发生了什么事
到表面？
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
Hmm. Huh?
唔。啊？
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Aw, gee, and I was so close.
噢，天啊，我是如此接近。
Hmm?
What is this place?
唔？
这是什么地方？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Oh!
哦！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
♪ ♪
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
[harp music]
[竖琴音乐]
♪ ♪
[laughs]
[笑]
This place is trash-tastic!
这个地方太垃圾了！
[cries out]
[喊叫]
Ow!
噢！
Oh, hey now!
哦，嘿现在！
Whoa-whoa-whoa-oh-oh!
哇-哇-哇-哦-哦！
- What's that?
- 那是什么？
[mysterious music]
[神秘的音乐]
- I don't know.
- 我不知道。
[twangy music]
[鼻音音乐]
- Hmm. [grunts]
- 唔。 [咕哝]
♪ ♪
- It's a gift!
- From the sky?
- 这是一份礼物！
- 从天上来的？
- From Neptune!
- 来自海王星！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
all: Yay!
全体：耶！
Aww.
哇。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
all: Thank you, Neptune!
全体：谢谢你，海王星！
["Here Comes the Bride" tune]
【《新娘来了》曲子】
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry, honey.
- 对不起，亲爱的。
I couldn't afford
the whole house.
我买不起
整个房子。
Just the door!
就在门口！
[mysterious music]
[神秘的音乐]
Whoa-ho-ho-ho!
Look at that!
哇-嗬-嗬-嗬！
看看那个！
- Now there's room
for my mother!
- 现在有空间了
为了我的妈妈！
- Whaa?
- 哇？
- Ehh...
- 呃...
♪ ♪
- Hmm? I thought
I saw something over--
- 唔？我以为
我看到了一些东西——
Ow!
噢！
- [raspy breathing]
- [粗重的呼吸]
- Hello?
Who are you?
- 你好？
你是谁？
- I'm King Neptune!
- 我是海王星国王！
Feel my power!
感受我的力量！
- Ow!
- 噢！
Old Man Jenkins?
老詹金斯？
- I'm not Old Man Jenkins
anymore!
- 我不是老詹金斯
不再了！
I'm King Neptune!
Take that!
我是海王星国王！
拿那个！
- [whimpers]
Huh?
- [呜咽]
啊？
All right, I'll play along.
好吧，我也跟着玩。
Hey, King Neptune!
I'm Poseidon!
嘿，海王星国王！
我是波塞冬！
[laughs]
[笑]
- Oh!
[grunts]
- 哦！
[咕哝]
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
[slide whistle]
[幻灯片哨子]
[lively music]
[活泼的音乐]
- Neptune is blessing us
with gifts and treasures!
- 海王星正在祝福我们
带着礼物和宝藏！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Surf's up, dude!
冲浪了，伙计！
♪ ♪
- Oh!
- 哦！
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
- Oh, yeah!
All right! Ho-ho!
- 哦，是的！
好的！嗬嗬！
- You say your desire
into the balloon,
- 你说出你的愿望
进入气球，
blow it up,
and send it to Neptune.
炸毁它，
并将其发送给海王星。
A slice of pizza.
一片披萨。
[gasps, exhales]
[喘气，呼气]
- A never-ending roll
of toilet paper.
- 永无休止的滚动
卫生纸。
[gasps, exhales]
[喘气，呼气]
♪ ♪
- A million grandmas.
- 一百万祖母。
[gasps, exhales]
[喘气，呼气]
♪ ♪
[both grunting, groaning]
[两人都咕哝着，呻吟着]
- You're not Poseidon.
- 你不是波塞冬。
You're SpongeBob SquarePants.
你是海绵宝宝。
- And you're
Old Man Jenkins!
- 而你是
老詹金斯！
- I was Old Man Jenkins
till I came here.
- 我是老詹金斯
直到我来到这里。
It was a year ago today...
一年前的今天了...
[twinkling music]
[闪烁的音乐]
all:
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
全部：
♪ 祝你生日快乐 ♪
- Oh, thank you, dea--
-哦，谢谢你，亲爱的--
Hello?
你好？
Some help, please?
请帮忙吗？
[all grumbling]
[大家都在抱怨]
- So now I gotta go back?
- 所以现在我得回去了？
I came all the way over here.
我千里迢迢来到这里。
- Hey--hey, come back.
- 嘿嘿，回来吧。
Come back, now!
快回来吧！
- Neptune,
I want a mustache.
- 海王星，
我想要胡子。
- Neptune, I want a cool voice.
- 海王星，我想要一个很酷的声音。
- Neptune, I want
another balloon.
- 海王星，我想要
另一个气球。
Now!
现在！
- My subjects!
I must get down to help them.
- 我的科目！
我必须下来帮助他们。
- Well, we could build a ladder
out of this stuff
- 好吧，我们可以建一个梯子
从这个东西中
and climb down--ooh,
uh, down?
然后爬下来——哦，
呃，下来？
- What are you, senile?
- 你是什么，老人？
- Uh-uh. I'm juvenile!
- 呃呃。我还未成年啊！
[laughs]
[笑]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[squeaking]
[吱吱声]
- Hey, what happened?
- What's going on here?
- 嘿，发生了什么事？
- 这是怎么回事？
- Why isn't Neptune sending
more gifts down for us?
- 为什么海王星不发送
还有更多礼物给我们吗？
- We must have upset him.
- 我们一定让他不高兴了。
- You must have upset him!
- 你一定让他不高兴了！
This is for you, Neptune.
这是给你的，海王星。
Oohh--
- Wait! Look!
哦哦——
- 等等！看！
[crowd gasps]
[人群喘息]
[excited chatter]
[兴奋的喋喋不休]
- Oh, it's the most amazing
thing I've ever seen.
- 哦，这是最神奇的
我见过的东西。
- What is it?
- 这是什么？
- What do you think it is?
- 你认为它是什么？
- It's a ladder
from Neptune!
- 这是一个梯子
来自海王星！
Let's climb up
and get more free stuff!
我们爬上去
并获得更多免费的东西！
- Me first!
[grunts]
- 我先！
[咕哝]
[laughing]
[笑]
[crowd murmuring]
[人群窃窃私语]
- [grunts]
Phew!
- [咕哝]
唷！
It took every piece of
the island to make this ladder.
花费了每一块
制作这个梯子的岛。
Ooh? Hey!
Look at that!
哦？嘿！
看看那个！
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
♪ ♪
I'm the first sponge
to ever do that!
我是第一块海绵
永远这样做！
- Big whoop.
- 大呼喊。
- Oh, yes!
It's the biggest whoop!
- 哦是的！
这是最大的欢呼！
Let's go home!
我们回家吧！
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
[rumbling]
[隆隆声]
- Stop shaking the ladder!
- 别摇晃梯子了！
- I'm not shaking it!
- 我不会摇晃它！
[mischievous music]
[恶作剧的音乐]
♪ ♪
- I think I see him!
It's Neptune!
- 我想我看到他了！
这是海王星！
- Oh, Neptune! Neptune!
- Out of my way!
- 哦，海王星！海王星！
- 别挡我的路！
[all chattering]
[大家都在喋喋不休]
- Wait a minute.
- 等一下。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- It's Old Man Jenkins!
- 这是老詹金斯！
- Old Man Jenkins
is Neptune?
——老詹金斯
是海王星吗？
- All hail
Old Man Jenkins!
- 万岁
老詹金斯！
- Get off my trash,
you idiots!
- 从我的垃圾堆里滚出来，
你们这些白痴！
- Praise Neptune!
We're all idiots for you!
- 赞美海王星！
在你眼里我们都是白痴！
all:
We're all idiots!
全部：
我们都是白痴！
We're all idiots!
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
Ooh-whaa!
噢-哇！
- Hey, it's SpongeBob!
- 嘿，这是海绵宝宝！
- Everybody climb back down.
There's nothing up there!
- 大家都爬下来。
上面什么也没有！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
I dove up and found
Old Man Jenkins
我潜入水中并发现
老詹金斯
living among
all these objects.
生活在
所有这些物体。
- Then it was you that you sent
these treasures down!
- 那么是你送来的
这些宝物落下！
- Hooray for SpongeBob!
He's our hero!
- 海绵宝宝万岁！
他是我们的英雄！
[all cheering]
[大家欢呼]
- No! Ahh!
- 不！啊！
Ohh--ow!
噢——噢！
Yahhh!
啊啊！
[sad music]
[悲伤的音乐]
♪ ♪
- I'm King Neptune!
- 我是海王星国王！
King of the seven seas,
七大洋之王，
the lakes, rivers, puddles...
湖泊、河流、水坑……
[spits]
[吐口水]
[ding]
[叮]
And spit too.
还吐口水。
I'm the king of spit!
我是口水王！
- So you're
the king of spit?
- 所以你是
吐口水之王？
[thunder booms]
[雷霆轰鸣]
- Uh-oh.
- 呃哦。
[seahorse neighs]
[海马嘶鸣]
- "Uh-oh" is right.
- “呃哦”是对的。
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
- [shouts]
- [喊叫]
[zapping]
[电击]
[sizzling]
[嘶嘶声]
- I smell like toast.
- 我闻起来像吐司。
Am I breakfast?
我是早餐吗？
[munching]
[咀嚼]
Needs jelly.
需要果冻。
[lively music]
[活泼的音乐]
- Hmm?
- 唔？
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Ooh, well, look at that.
哦，好吧，看看那个。
Someone threw away a perfectly
good SpongeBob standee.
有人完美地扔掉了
海绵宝宝的好站姿。
[laughs]
[笑]
Yagh!
呀！
Oof! Ugh.
钱币！啊。
♪ ♪
- They called me a hero.
- 他们称我为英雄。
[jazzy music]
[爵士乐]
♪ ♪
- Ooh--[gasps]
- 哦--[喘气]
Ooh--[gasps]
Yeah!
哦——[喘气]
是啊！
Don't you just love
cleaning day?
你不就是爱吗
清洁日？
- We're so lucky.
- 我们真幸运。
- Aww.
- 哇。
Mr. Krabs's first dollar.
蟹老板的第一块钱。
[squeaking]
[吱吱声]
Whaa?
哇？
♪ ♪
Huh?
啊？
♪ ♪
- Don't forget to clean
the safe, boys.
- 别忘了清洁
保险箱，孩子们。
And keep your eyes on the
Krabby Patty Secret Formula!
并密切关注
蟹黄饼秘密配方！
♪ ♪
-Hey, we need
the combination!
-嘿，我们需要
组合！
- I got it covered.
- 我把它盖住了。
[snaps]
[快照]
- Nyah!
- 呀！
- [hums]
Doink!
- [哼哼]
多因克！
[chuckling]
[轻笑]
Mm. Mm-hmm.
毫米。嗯嗯。
Voilà.
瞧。
- Ahh--ooh!
- 啊——哦！
- See? This is fun!
- 看？这很有趣！
- [evil laughter]
- [邪恶的笑声]
Krabs will never
see me coming!
螃蟹永远不会
看到我来了！
Presso-inviso!
Presso-inviso！
[mysterious music]
[神秘的音乐]
[humming]
Ahh!
[嗡嗡声]
啊！
Can't see my own feet.
看不到自己的脚。
- Mm-hmm.
- 嗯嗯。
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
Don't you go anywhere
while I clean your homey-womey.
你别去任何地方
当我清理你的家的时候。
- Out of sight...
- 看不见...
- [evil laugh]
- [邪恶的笑声]
- Out of my mind.
=> - 从我的脑海中消失。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Hey, watch it!
嘿，注意看！
[blubbers]
Hommina-wah?
[哭声]
霍米纳哇？
The Secret Formula!
秘密配方！
Must be one of Krabs's tricks!
这肯定是蟹蟹的诡计之一！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
He'll pop out any second now.
他现在随时都会跳出来。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Well?
出色地？
[crickets chirping]
[蟋蟀鸣叫]
Nothing. All right.
没有什么。好的。
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
I really did it!
我真的做到了！
Hey, Karen, guess what!
嘿，凯伦，你猜怎么着！
I finally got the Krabby Patty
Secret Formula.
我终于吃到蟹黄饼了
秘密配方。
How you like me now?
你现在怎么样？
[electronic warbling]
[电子颤音]
- It's genuine.
- 这是正品。
Come here, you big hunk
of aquatic organism!
过来，你这个大块头
水生生物！
Ooh, I knew you could do it!
哦，我知道你能做到！
[smooching]
[接吻]
Just don't blow it this time.
只是这次别吹了。
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
Oh! Oh! Ahh!
哦！哦！啊！
Hey, Squidward,
嘿，章鱼哥，
have you seen the Krabby Patty
Secret Formula?
你见过蟹黄饼吗
秘密配方？
Ohh!
哦！
I put it right here in this
circular file cabinet.
我把它放在这里
圆形文件柜。
- That's a trash can,
you nitwit!
- 那是一个垃圾桶，
你这个白痴！
The formula!
公式！
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
- Face it, SpongeBob!
The formula...
- 面对现实吧，海绵宝宝！
公式...
- Don't say it!
- Is gone.
- 别说！
- 走了。
- Oh. I asked you
not to say it.
- 哦。我问你
不说了。
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
Why would you even do that?
你为什么要这么做？
- Come on.
- 快点。
Now let's see if the security
cameras picked anything up.
现在让我们看看安全性是否
摄像机拍到了任何东西。
[whirs, clicks]
[呼呼声，咔哒声]
Hmm.
- [gasps]
唔。
- [喘气]
- Hi!
- 你好！
I'd like to order--hmm--
我想订购--嗯--
half a Krabby Patty, please!
请吃半个蟹黄饼！
Oh, thank you.
[laughs]
哦，谢谢。
[笑]
[munching]
[咀嚼]
- [giggles]
- [咯咯笑]
- [munching]
- [咀嚼]
[both exclaim, groan]
[两人惊呼，呻吟]
♪ ♪
- Ah! It's alive!
- 啊！它还活着！
- Hold on.
- 坚持，稍等。
Plankton?
- Ahh!
浮游生物？
- 啊！
[gasping]
What are we gonna do?
[喘气]
我们要做什么？
- [gasping]
- [喘气]
Okay. All right.
好的。好的。
We'll just pretend everything's
normal until closing time.
我们就假装一切如常
正常直到关门时间。
Then we'll steal the formula
back from Plankton!
然后我们就窃取公式
从浮游生物回来了！
Yeah.
是的。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Come on! Open up!
快点！打开！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[chomps]
Ahh!
[咀嚼]
啊！
♪ ♪
Open Sesame.
芝麻开门。
♪ ♪
It's no use, Karen.
It won't budge.
这是没有用的，凯伦。
它不会让步。
- Of course not, Einstein,
it has a time lock.
- 当然不是，爱因斯坦，
它有一个时间锁。
It won't open until
tomorrow morning.
直到
明天早上。
- Well, I've waited this long.
- 嗯，我等了这么久了。
What's a few more
还有几个啥
excruciatingly long hours?
工作时间长得令人难以忍受？
- Night, Mr. Krabs.
- 晚安，蟹老板。
Sleep tight.
睡个好觉。
- Don't let the
bed urchins bite.
- 不要让
床上的海胆会咬人。
- Eh, sure.
- 呃，当然。
You, too, you two.
你们也一样，你们两个。
[engine whirring]
[引擎的呼呼声]
[both laughing nervously]
[两人紧张地笑]
- Okay, let's go get
that formula.
- 好吧，我们去吧
那个公式。
- Ooh, we are gonna
pull a Plankton on Plankton!
- 哦，我们要去
把浮游生物拉到浮游生物上！
[laughs]
[笑]
[sneaky music]
[偷偷摸摸的音乐]
[cat yowls]
- Nyah! Whaa?
[猫叫声]
- 呀！哇？
- Sorry. [laughs]
- 对不起。 [笑]
Stepped on my tail.
踩到了我的尾巴。
- What are you wearing?
- 你将如何穿着？
- I'm a cat burglar!
- 我是一只猫贼！
[purring]
[咕噜声]
Okay, I'll change.
好吧，我会改变的。
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Hang on.
Ooh.
- 不挂断。
哦。
- And just how am I
supposed to get in?
- 我怎么样
应该进去吗？
Ooh!
哦！
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
♪ ♪
[spooky music]
[诡异的音乐]
- Ahh!
- 啊！
♪ ♪
- Yeah, yeah,
now eat her brain!
- 是啊，是啊，
现在吃掉她的大脑！
[sighs]
I love a good romance.
[叹气]
我喜欢美好的浪漫。
[yawns, grunts]
[打哈欠，咕哝]
♪ ♪
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
[gargling]
[漱口]
♪ ♪
[both yelp]
[两人都尖叫]
♪ ♪
both: Phew.
两人：唷。
[ding]
[叮]
- Goodnight, honey.
- 晚安，亲爱的。
[smooches]
[亲吻]
- [snoring]
- [打鼾]
[sneaky music]
[偷偷摸摸的音乐]
♪ ♪
- What are you doing?
- 你在干什么？
- Making sure he's asleep.
- 确保他睡着了。
- [snoring]
- [打鼾]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
♪ ♪
[growling]
[咆哮]
- Yeesh!
[gulps]
- 是啊！
[吞咽]
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
Aww, it's Plankton's
little pet, Spot.
哇，这是浮游生物的
小宠物，斑点。
He wants to play!
他想玩！
- Will you get him off of me?
- 你能让他离开我吗？
- Hmm. Ahh!
- 唔。啊！
[whistles]
Get the stick, boy!
[口哨声]
拿起棍子，孩子！
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
[barking]
[叫声]
- Fetch!
- 拿来！
- Look out!
- 小心！
- Diodes...zebras...
- 二极管...斑马...
Make a new batch of chum...
[snores]
做一批新的密友...
[打鼾]
- It's okay.
She's in sleep mode.
- 没关系。
她正处于睡眠模式。
- Oh, dear,
the chum is escaping.
- 哦，亲爱的，
密友正在逃跑。
[both exclaim]
[两人惊呼]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
[sneaky music]
[偷偷摸摸的音乐]
♪ ♪
- This must be it.
- 一定是这个。
[alarm blares]
[警报声]
- Remain still for retina scan.
- 保持静止进行视网膜扫描。
- Now what'll we do?
- Good thing I brought this!
- 现在我们该怎么办？
- 还好我带了这个！
They really captured the cute
little dimple on his chin.
他们真的捕捉到了可爱
下巴上有一个小酒窝。
- Looks like they captured
the rest of him too!
- 看起来他们捕获了
他的其余部分也是如此！
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- Oh!
- 哦！
- I'll take it from here.
- 我会从这里拿走它。
- I'm fine.
- 我很好。
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
You go first this time.
这次你先走。
- Hmm-mmph.
- 嗯嗯。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- You okay?
- No!
- 你还好吗？
- 不！
♪ ♪
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
Ow.
噢。
- I'm standing still!
I'm not even doing anything!
- 我站着不动！
我什至什么也没做！
[foghorn blows]
[雾号吹响]
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
- Heh...sorry.
- 呃...抱歉。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Ahh.
啊。
I can't believe
that actually worked!
我不敢相信
这确实有效！
[alarm blaring]
[警报声]
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
[both groaning]
[两人都呻吟]
[cheery music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Good morning, Krusty crew!
- 早上好，Krusty 船员！
Ready to cook up a
new batch of Krabby Patties?
准备煮一个
新一批蟹黄饼？
Er...
呃……
Why are you two
smoldering?
为什么你们两个
闷烧？
- We're sorry, Mr. Krabs!
- 很抱歉，蟹老板！
- No, he's delirious!
- 不，他神志不清！
He doesn't know
what he's saying.
他不知道
他在说什么。
- No! Mr. Krabs
deserves the truth.
- 不！蟹老板先生
值得真相。
We accidentally threw away
the Krabby Patty Formula
我们不小心扔掉了
蟹黄饼配方
and Plankton found it!
浮游生物发现了它！
We tried to steal it back,
but we failed!
我们试图把它偷回来
但我们失败了！
- You did what?
- 你做了什么？
Plankton stole me formula?
浮游生物偷了我的配方奶粉？
- That's what he said.
Yeah.
- 他就是这么说的。
是的。
- Then I'll just
have to steal it back.
- 那我就
必须把它偷回来。
[relaxing music]
[轻松的音乐]
Hmm. Uh-huh.
唔。嗯嗯。
[grunts]
Oh.
[咕哝]
哦。
[smooches]
Don't worry.
[亲吻]
别担心。
Papa's here.
爸爸来了。
[rooster crow]
[公鸡打鸣]
- Oh, yeah!
- 哦，是的！
Who's the man?
那个男人是谁？
You are!
你是！
Eh, man.
呃，伙计。
- [barking]
- [吠叫]
- No, no, no!
- 不，不，不！
Krabs!
螃蟹们！
- [sighs] I'm sure glad
the formula is back
- [叹气]我很高兴
公式又回来了
in the safe where it belongs,
Mr. Krabs.
在它所属的保险箱里，
蟹老板。
- [laughs]
Me, too, boyo.
- [笑]
我也是，小伙子。
And to make sure
you two don't ever
并确保
你们两个从来没有
take your eyes off it again,
I have a surprise for you.
再次把目光从它身上移开
我有一个惊喜给你。
You're me new security system.
你是我的新安全系统。
[laughs]
[笑]
- Yay!
- Wait!
- 耶！
- 等待！
I'm claustrophobic!
我有幽闭恐惧症！
[relaxed music]
[轻松的音乐]
♪ ♪